The Reaper
The first day I began working...
...at the slaughterhouse,
That night I was dreaming
that I was here...
...in the slaughterhouse.
The animals came in and they
starred at me...
saying "what's up? now it's your turn".
Meaning that they were looking at me
like if I was an animal.
Those are dreams that one has.
But they most be for some reason.
When I arrived to the slaughterhouse,
I labeled my boots "the Pinocchio"...
...and then came one of my
coworkers and said...
..."no, you are going to be the reaper",
from then they started calling me
the reaper... reaper,
that's how it stayed, for murderer.
I am afraid of death.
Yes, because one goes to work, right?...
but you don't know if you are
going to come back home.
...and when its your turn to
died, you just died.
It's because one's stayed
there, in the street.
Its when life its over and the reaper
came to take you to death.
It's like going around the world.
Because when we died
this world is over,
you don't see it ever again.
People say in this world,
there is glory and hell.
For me, that is a lie.
When I die, my world it's over.
Hell is what I live here.
At the top I can be stronger but
being down in the cage...
...they're stronger than you.
Because they're in the little box,
I mean, they're shut in there.
In the little box, you can
kill them.
And you can be stronger.
At the top yes,
but when you're down
not anymore.
Down there in the cage the
animal is stronger than you.
I lived my father's loss,
like the word looked very
small to me.
I went walking through the street,
thinking only about him.
Little by little I started
getting rid of that idea,
when I started seeing my children,
I am going to take care them...
...because my father now is resting,
and my childrens?...
...they're going to stay suffering,
I could get sick any moment and
then, it's all over.
I think everyone can kill,
having the experience.
The only thing is getting the experience,
and then everyone can kill.
Like me that I already know.
It has been 20 years, 30 years.
For a beginner which only has two years,
the bull's going to escape.
When my sister died,
I felt bad when I killed the bulls..
...because one sees the animals,
and then figures that one
is going to end like that,
Like an animal.
Because an animal feels like you do.
Even if you are hitting it
and hitting it,
feels just like you do.
When I kill the bulls,
they cry,
and they get a tear on their eyes.
I mean, you kill a bull
and they get tears.
l think a person is the same...
...and its pain that is not endured
by bulls or any other animals.
The first time I came to the slaughterhouse...
...I was coming from my house,
I passed by the slaughterhouse
and I saw a sign...
...that said that they needed workers...
so I asked for a job and they
say yes, come tomorrow...
...and I got the job.
I started here sweeping the corrals,
and then I got interested on
how they killed the bulls.
So I asked them if they borrowed
me the knife and I killed one.
Since then I liked to kill bulls.
My family thinks that my job is dangerous,
that's why they tell me to quick my job.
With this job l have been hurt,
because of what happens there...
...they're accidents and it is dangerous,
that's why my family its
always taking care of me.
I would never kill a human being...
...because it's not an animal,
it's not a bull.
I mean, the bulls l kill its
because of the economic need.
Yes, because if I do not kill,
then I and my family don't eat.
Efrain, kills every day between
500 hundreds bulls,
6 days a week, since 25 years ago.